So now the result season has started.   That
means companies will release their results.
Results of many companies are going to come this week.   There are
many companies including HDFC Bank, ICIC Bank, IDA, Infosys and Tata Alexi
which will release their results.
So let's discuss how he performed in Quarter 3.  We will
also
talk about the date on which their results will be declared.
So before starting the discussion I
would like to say that if you have not subscribed to our channel
then please
subscribe and also press the bell icon.
So let's talk about some companies
that will release their results.  There are
companies in the IT sector.  Infosys, Wipro
and banking sector companies like
HDFC Bank, ICIC Bank as well as HDFC
Life Insurance Company will also release their March
quarter numbers.  Along with this,
companies like HDFC Asset Management Company, ICIC Lambar General Insurance Company, ICIC PSI, Tata Alexi MST, India Renewable Energy Development Agency i.e. Arida, Enjel Renewable Technology, Indosolar, Mahindra EPC Irrigation Network, 18 Media & Investment and Yes Bank will release their results.
If we talk about Ada this week,
Ada will release its results on 15th April
i.e. Tuesday.  The PSU company had reported a
jump in net profit year-on-year to nearly 27%, up from 26% in the same quarter last year.  In the third quarter, the
company's net profit was ₹425 crore,
which was ₹335 crore in the third quarter of last year.  The
ad PAT
saw a jump of 10% and its total
revenue from operations was ₹1698 crore.  There was a
jump of 35% in this.
Apart from this, GM Beverages will also release its results.  The
company will see its results on Tuesday, April 15.  The
company's revenue
saw a growth of 5.7% in the December quarter.  The
company recorded revenue of ₹16 crore.
However, the company's net profit declined by
around ₹0.45%.
Talking about earnings before tax, interest, depreciation and amortization, it had
increased by 18% year on year.
If we talk about Infosys, then Infosys will
release its quarterly results on April 17.
In quarter 3, the company
showed a growth of 11.5% in its net profit.  Revenue also
grew by 7.5% and the company raised its guidance to
4.5% to 5%
for fiscal year 2025.  Wipro will release its
quarterly results on
Wednesday, April 16.  The
company's revenue for Q3 was ₹
2629 million, which was in line with estimates.
Constant currency growth was
seen at 0.1%.  This was also
seen around the estimate.  The company's revenue in rupee terms was
₹22,265 crore.  That means it was
seen increasing by 0.4% quarter on quarter.
EBIT was up 5.5% quarter on quarter.  The
improvement in margins was also
decent.   It was
17.5%.  So all these things will
remain in it.  People will keep an eye on this too.
ICICI Bank, ICIC LBR General Insurance,
ICICI Principal Life
Insurance and three ICICI Group
companies will declare their quarterly results.
This will be seen on April 15, the
results of ICICI Bank
and the results of these companies of ICICI Bank will be
seen on April 15.  Whereas the
results of ICICI Bank will be declared on Saturday i.e. 19th
April.
Talking about HDFC Bank, it will also
release its results this week on
April 19, i.e. Saturday.
HDFC Bank results will be announced on that day.  The
results of all three companies, i.e. HDFC AMC and HDFC L Insurance, will be seen.
So if we talk about HDFC Bank, the
company's net interest income increased by 8% year on year in quarter 3.   It was
₹6653 crore which was around expectations.
Its net profit increased by 2% year on year.
₹16736 crore was seen.   At
the same time, the asset quality was
seen to be a little weak.  Its gross NPA had
increased slightly and net NPA had also
increased.  So if you want, you can keep an eye on this also
because people will keep an eye on it.
Now let's talk about es bank.  The
bank will release its results on Saturday, April 19.
Talking about its recent quarter 3, the company's net
profit was ₹612 crore.  A significant
increase was seen in this.  Its
estimate was around Rs 538 crore.  A
good increase was
seen in this.  There was an
improvement of 165% in the net profit of the company.  This time
Tata Alexi will also release its results.   The
company will release its results on April 17.
So, the net profit of this Tata Group company
in quarter 3 had a
growth of around 13.25% to 5.25%.  ₹199
crore was seen.  So this is a big update.  It will remain
in it.  You can keep an eye on this too if you want.
So these were the news about some companies about
when they will release their results
and what was their performance in quarter three.  I
hope
you liked our video.  Don't
forget to tell me how you liked it.  Also
subscribe to our channel.
Press the bell icon.
Thank you very much for watching the video.  We